<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Ted Slocum's personal website and blog, where he thinks online.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Special Categories</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Never missing a chance to think that I am special, today I thought &lt;em&gt;I am so lucky to have a lot of people in my life that defy categorization. Neither friend nor family is a sufficient word.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this thought is so silly and obvious to rightfully be called absurd, I would like to think that the underlying sentiment is not too hokey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sentiment has to do with the fact that the categories of friends and family both are essentially infinite. Within each group you can have such varying relationships and characters. And that while if you asked me “well, is he a friend or a part of your family?” I could answer you, that answer is so zoomed out that it looses most of it’s beauty.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/16/Special-Categories</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/16/Special-Categories</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Envy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The hippie mind thinks that envy and admiration are different in kind. Envy is not deep, meaningful, or healthy. Admiration is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The practical mind thinks that they are probably very closely related psychologically and that the difference is more fluff that substance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways… this weekend finding myself covered in envy-admiration, I was struck multiple times by the feeling that I still not who I want to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is quite okay by me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/15/Envy</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/15/Envy</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take Advantage</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In a strange and rare moment yesterday my mind bounced from &lt;em&gt;that doesn’t make any sense&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;em&gt;Ohhh, I like that about myself&lt;/em&gt;. Let me attempt to explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had just finished expressing how I love that I walk everywhere in my life, when I was expressing that one of the things I was looking forward to in the next couple years is the fact that I will spend a lot of time driving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter, &lt;em&gt;that doesn’t make any sense&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Split second…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter, &lt;em&gt;wait, that is actually pretty cool. I am not attached to one or the other, rather, I can find joy in taking advantage of both when appropriate&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/14/Take-Advantage</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/14/Take-Advantage</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food and Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am finding it is hard to encapsulate any real wisdom regarding the role of food in our lives. It cuts across so many domains - social, economic, biological, scientific, and philosophical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I really want to plant some flags and have some strong positions here. Not having a solid and stable relationship with food seems to be a large source of discontent for myself and many loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My (few) initial leads are moderation, being kind to yourself, understanding habits and addiction, and developing an appreciation of what modern research has to say on the biological side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully more to come…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/13/Food-Life</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/13/Food-Life</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exciting Scale</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Part of the allure of starting a journey into the world of web is the scale and reach. Well established is the idea that the human mind is poor at comprehending things that are very large. Each time I see thousands of people online playing a game together, the 1B download badge next to instagram in the google play store, or 100’s of contributors to a github repository my mind says &lt;em&gt;wow, I have no idea, do I&lt;/em&gt;. Exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/12/Exciting-Scale</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/12/Exciting-Scale</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seth's Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you read this blog daily and do not read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.seths.blog&quot;&gt;Seths Godin’s blog&lt;/a&gt; I beg you to do the opposite. If you still feel like reading mine afterwards, bonus, but please please read his first. No disservice of trying to describe it, I will only say that I greatly value getting to look at the world through his eyeballs every day. Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/11/Seths-Blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/11/Seths-Blog</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bloggers Block</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the first time on this blogging adventure I have run in to the thought &lt;em&gt;I don’t know what to write about today&lt;/em&gt;. It makes me feel boring and shallow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think of friends whom seem to have a much richer and interesting life with a multitude of friends, projects, and aspirations. Surely they have infinite things to write about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly my life is very routinized and repetitive from a birds-eye-view. However, on the inside each routine has it’s small variations that are the source of richness. And each repetition feels like it is slowly leading to a new and beautiful place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;em&gt;problem&lt;/em&gt; is that I don’t have the language abilities to express this &lt;em&gt;richness&lt;/em&gt; without sounding hokey, woo-wooie, or off my rocker insane. But I suppose that is part of this adventure, to gain this ability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/10/Bloggers-Block</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/10/Bloggers-Block</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thank You Jonny</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A few photos and a gleeful thank you out to Mr. Jonny Spicer. Thanks for a lovely dinner. Forturnately Jonny mis-stepped and &lt;a href=&quot;https://tedslocum.com/daily/2020/02/11/Win&quot;&gt;lost our bet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vday-0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Valentine's Day Dinner 0&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vday-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Valentine's Day Dinner 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/09/Thank-You-Jonny</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/09/Thank-You-Jonny</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Colegiales</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just as I am falling in love with my neighborhood here in Buenos Aires, we are moving. While it was not love at first sight - it has taken my a full year and a half to fall in love - I would proudly defend Colegiales as &lt;strong&gt;the best neighborhood&lt;/strong&gt; vs any and all willing challengers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to name a few things it has going for it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great bakery. Which as the factory for all it’s franchise locations. This is not a trivial factoid, it means that every day some yummy beautiful treat is on sale. 2 for 1.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A perfect corner grocery store. Organic, with all the essentials, and rarities to inspire you in the kitchen. Also the owner and staff are lovely.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coffee shops on almost every corner.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Local restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Little traffic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tree-lined streets.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A beautiful plaza.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy access to the rest of the city (train stop, buses, subway, city-bikes).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cheap rent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multiple places to get a good burger.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A fancy restaurant for special occasions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bars of every type.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of schools.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The streets are always clean.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great co-working space.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Houses, apartments, townhouses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great yoga studio.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cheap gyms, expensive gyms and everything in between.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NO HIPSTERS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on. But the bottom line is that I have loved living here and will remember fondly the life Colegiales.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/08/Colegiales</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/08/Colegiales</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoga - Beginner's Mind</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am thoroughly enjoying my growing yoga routine. My body feels powerful and relaxed and my mind feels renewed and fresh after each practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wanting to go a bit deeper, I picked up a yoga book and I’m not sure that was a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to document my first impressions here and see if they change over time (as green cult entrant’s minds have been known to do).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The principles are inspiring and motivating - lean into pain rather than turn away, consistency, body-mind connection, self responsibility, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The philosophical doctrine seems beyond goofy and woo-woo beyond belief. Where as you can take other religious ideas as metaphor, it is hard to see the metaphor in &lt;em&gt;blocked emotions are located in pelvic chakras&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The philosophy has similarities to Buddhism - uprooting negative aspects of the mind and the emphasis on experience as the highest form of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going to stick with the book and the practice and see if I can’t separate what I perceive as dogma from the real benefits. Check back in in a few months.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/07/Yoga-Philosophy-0</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/07/Yoga-Philosophy-0</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>