<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Ted Slocum's personal website and blog, where he thinks online.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Not Cool Brother - Cherry Pie</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of the time when you say &lt;em&gt;too soon&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;not cool&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;that’s just not right&lt;/em&gt; you never actually ever think of the thing that caused the reaction again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today that is not the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning I received this image just as my appetite was coming alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cherry-pie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mrs Rowe's Cherry&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sender knew full well how much I enjoy Mrs Rowe’s Cherry Pie and that I have no reasonable way of satisfying the mouth-watering-desire that the image would surely cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My belly is rumbling and my mouth is still watering hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not cool&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/06/Not-Nice</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/06/Not-Nice</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extra Kind Hour</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Idea: Extra Kind Hour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not a big drinker, but I do often get aggressive and unkind in the evening! A beer would not help my cause, but being extra kind and receiving extra-kindness in return would be great. This is especially true during typical happy hour hours. So…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of March - Extra Kind Hour (6pm-10pm, Monday-Friday)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/05/Extra-Kind-Hour</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/05/Extra-Kind-Hour</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Influencers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The term &lt;em&gt;influencer&lt;/em&gt; always leaves my mouth as a four-letter-word, but I am starting to think that I am wrong in my condemnation. The truth is that I am actively looking for more and better &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt; in my life, as I think they are extremely valuable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cynically, they are sales-men in disguise, selling you under false or shallow pretenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But on the other hand, it is inevitable that we are influenced by those around us (we compare, judge, and envy). So why not choose our &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the idea is: choose &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt;! But carefully and consciously.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/04/Influencers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/04/Influencers</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why am I doing xyz?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Why am I doing x, y, or z?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often I worry that the answer is, &lt;em&gt;so I can say that I am&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good thing about this problem is that it is easy to prove my motivations are genuine.
Simply try to stop sharing your projects and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it hard to not share? Do you get more or less from them when you don’t share?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/03/Why-Projects</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/03/Why-Projects</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lovely asymmetry</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Concisely, love never requires reasons, anger does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poetically, anger rests atop a tall weak foundation of faulty logic, ready to crumble. Love floats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rationally, there is always a reason you are angry. But our best understanding of how the world works undermines all reasons completely - it could be no other way. When I can be no other way, anger dissipates, love does not.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/02/The-happy-asymmetry</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/02/The-happy-asymmetry</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practical definition of love</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While defining &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; seems silly, having a useful definition does not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love defined as &lt;em&gt;the quality of attention you give to something&lt;/em&gt; is the most useful definition I have come across because it is measurable and correctable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I did not love my work. I was simply going through the motions - the quality of my attention was low and poor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/01/Practical-definition-of-love</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/01/Practical-definition-of-love</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stress of Moving</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;More than once I have been told that moving induces more stress than about any other major life event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stress has not yet arrived, but my mind is frantically searching for ways to avoid its arrival indefinitely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Always keep in mind (or at least in your pocket) the beautiful reason you are moving.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Decide what is important during this process. Let the rest fall where it may.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good upfront communication and knowing what is important to your partner.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This is a new chance to decide again what stuff really matters and what stuff to allow into our lives. Be grateful.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Not every decision is best made together. Delegate where appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/29/Stress-of-Moving</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/29/Stress-of-Moving</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Simple Problem</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I like having &lt;em&gt;simple&lt;/em&gt; as an objective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Simple&lt;/em&gt;, to me, is a close cousin to tranquility, virtue, compassion, meaning, and beauty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem with &lt;em&gt;simple&lt;/em&gt; is that the world is not so. &lt;em&gt;Simple&lt;/em&gt; can always be effectively undermined by one word - why - leading to the messiness and complexity of the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the goal can’t be simply &lt;em&gt;simple&lt;/em&gt;. It is more like containing the complexity of the world in your version of &lt;em&gt;simple&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/28/The-Simple-Problem</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/28/The-Simple-Problem</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buddha Biography - Notes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Memorable Ideas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The benefit of having a group around him that was also searching for spiritual development… Community.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The stark difference between theory and practice. Between knowledge and direct knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Lack of personality somehow equates to charisma.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Have no idols. Have a Dharma.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Meditative skills don’t directly equate to ethics.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The middle path. Between indulgence and asceticism.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To reject dogma without rejecting those who embrace dogmas. A new onboard-speech to the Dharma for each unique student.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best line:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;[Don’t worship me when I am dead. Just] remember me as one who has woken up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/27/Buddha-Bio</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/27/Buddha-Bio</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Proud</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday my girlfriend was accepted to grad school. It was a day filled with joy, hugs, and tears. It is not an exaggeration to say that it is an opportunity of a lifetime for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the excitement wears off I find myself feeling very proud of her, but not in the way I would have thought. I am not proud of her for &lt;em&gt;getting in&lt;/em&gt;, but I am proud of the &lt;em&gt;hope she permitted herself to have&lt;/em&gt;. I am not proud of her &lt;em&gt;good test scores&lt;/em&gt;, but I am proud of that she &lt;em&gt;studied and showed up for the test&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/26/Proud</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/26/Proud</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>