<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Ted Slocum's personal website and blog, where he thinks online.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Exciting Scale</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Part of the allure of starting a journey into the world of web is the scale and reach. Well established is the idea that the human mind is poor at comprehending things that are very large. Each time I see thousands of people online playing a game together, the 1B download badge next to instagram in the google play store, or 100’s of contributors to a github repository my mind says &lt;em&gt;wow, I have no idea, do I&lt;/em&gt;. Exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/12/Exciting-Scale</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/12/Exciting-Scale</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seth's Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you read this blog daily and do not read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.seths.blog&quot;&gt;Seths Godin’s blog&lt;/a&gt; I beg you to do the opposite. If you still feel like reading mine afterwards, bonus, but please please read his first. No disservice of trying to describe it, I will only say that I greatly value getting to look at the world through his eyeballs every day. Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/11/Seths-Blog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/11/Seths-Blog</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bloggers Block</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the first time on this blogging adventure I have run in to the thought &lt;em&gt;I don’t know what to write about today&lt;/em&gt;. It makes me feel boring and shallow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think of friends whom seem to have a much richer and interesting life with a multitude of friends, projects, and aspirations. Surely they have infinite things to write about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truly my life is very routinized and repetitive from a birds-eye-view. However, on the inside each routine has it’s small variations that are the source of richness. And each repetition feels like it is slowly leading to a new and beautiful place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;em&gt;problem&lt;/em&gt; is that I don’t have the language abilities to express this &lt;em&gt;richness&lt;/em&gt; without sounding hokey, woo-wooie, or off my rocker insane. But I suppose that is part of this adventure, to gain this ability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/10/Bloggers-Block</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/10/Bloggers-Block</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thank You Jonny</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A few photos and a gleeful thank you out to Mr. Jonny Spicer. Thanks for a lovely dinner. Forturnately Jonny mis-stepped and &lt;a href=&quot;https://tedslocum.com/daily/2020/02/11/Win&quot;&gt;lost our bet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vday-0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Valentine's Day Dinner 0&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vday-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Valentine's Day Dinner 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/09/Thank-You-Jonny</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/09/Thank-You-Jonny</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Colegiales</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just as I am falling in love with my neighborhood here in Buenos Aires, we are moving. While it was not love at first sight - it has taken my a full year and a half to fall in love - I would proudly defend Colegiales as &lt;strong&gt;the best neighborhood&lt;/strong&gt; vs any and all willing challengers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to name a few things it has going for it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great bakery. Which as the factory for all it’s franchise locations. This is not a trivial factoid, it means that every day some yummy beautiful treat is on sale. 2 for 1.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A perfect corner grocery store. Organic, with all the essentials, and rarities to inspire you in the kitchen. Also the owner and staff are lovely.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coffee shops on almost every corner.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Local restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Little traffic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tree-lined streets.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A beautiful plaza.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy access to the rest of the city (train stop, buses, subway, city-bikes).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cheap rent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multiple places to get a good burger.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A fancy restaurant for special occasions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bars of every type.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of schools.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The streets are always clean.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great co-working space.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Houses, apartments, townhouses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A great yoga studio.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cheap gyms, expensive gyms and everything in between.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;NO HIPSTERS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could go on and on. But the bottom line is that I have loved living here and will remember fondly the life Colegiales.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/08/Colegiales</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/08/Colegiales</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoga - Beginner's Mind</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am thoroughly enjoying my growing yoga routine. My body feels powerful and relaxed and my mind feels renewed and fresh after each practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wanting to go a bit deeper, I picked up a yoga book and I’m not sure that was a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to document my first impressions here and see if they change over time (as green cult entrant’s minds have been known to do).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The principles are inspiring and motivating - lean into pain rather than turn away, consistency, body-mind connection, self responsibility, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The philosophical doctrine seems beyond goofy and woo-woo beyond belief. Where as you can take other religious ideas as metaphor, it is hard to see the metaphor in &lt;em&gt;blocked emotions are located in pelvic chakras&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The philosophy has similarities to Buddhism - uprooting negative aspects of the mind and the emphasis on experience as the highest form of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going to stick with the book and the practice and see if I can’t separate what I perceive as dogma from the real benefits. Check back in in a few months.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/07/Yoga-Philosophy-0</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/07/Yoga-Philosophy-0</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not Cool Brother - Cherry Pie</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of the time when you say &lt;em&gt;too soon&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;not cool&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;that’s just not right&lt;/em&gt; you never actually ever think of the thing that caused the reaction again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today that is not the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning I received this image just as my appetite was coming alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cherry-pie.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mrs Rowe's Cherry&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sender knew full well how much I enjoy Mrs Rowe’s Cherry Pie and that I have no reasonable way of satisfying the mouth-watering-desire that the image would surely cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My belly is rumbling and my mouth is still watering hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not cool&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/06/Not-Nice</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/06/Not-Nice</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extra Kind Hour</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Idea: Extra Kind Hour!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not a big drinker, but I do often get aggressive and unkind in the evening! A beer would not help my cause, but being extra kind and receiving extra-kindness in return would be great. This is especially true during typical happy hour hours. So…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of March - Extra Kind Hour (6pm-10pm, Monday-Friday)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/05/Extra-Kind-Hour</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/05/Extra-Kind-Hour</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Influencers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The term &lt;em&gt;influencer&lt;/em&gt; always leaves my mouth as a four-letter-word, but I am starting to think that I am wrong in my condemnation. The truth is that I am actively looking for more and better &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt; in my life, as I think they are extremely valuable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cynically, they are sales-men in disguise, selling you under false or shallow pretenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But on the other hand, it is inevitable that we are influenced by those around us (we compare, judge, and envy). So why not choose our &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the idea is: choose &lt;em&gt;influencers&lt;/em&gt;! But carefully and consciously.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/04/Influencers</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/04/Influencers</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why am I doing xyz?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Why am I doing x, y, or z?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often I worry that the answer is, &lt;em&gt;so I can say that I am&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good thing about this problem is that it is easy to prove my motivations are genuine.
Simply try to stop sharing your projects and see what happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it hard to not share? Do you get more or less from them when you don’t share?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/03/Why-Projects</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/03/03/Why-Projects</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>