<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Ted Slocum's personal website and blog, where he thinks online.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Advice Tides</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A disturbing phenomenon I have been noticing lately: At times I am open to suggestions and advice, at others I am closed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this seems obvious and sane, my discernment seems arbitrary and way off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Openness to input should be based on some objective measure, not solely the tides of mind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/21/Advice-Tides</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/21/Advice-Tides</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physical Health Thank You Note</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I would like to thank a few people that I in my estimation have the most to do with my current physical health, which today is the object of great joy and gratitude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First my parents for my genes, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second my funcional teachers. Among other things you have taught me how to get stronger where it matters, how to rest, and how to not chronically injure yourself while exercising. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third to my yoga instructor and massage therapist. To be honest I have no idea what these activities are doing for me other that making me feel better. None the less, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally to my partner who not only puts up with my obsession and rituals related to sleep, but facilitates them. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/20/Physical-Thank-You</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/20/Physical-Thank-You</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markers of a Fit Mind</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What are the markers of a fit mind?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Physically we have strength, flexibility, endurance, and resilience as generally agreed upon measurable characteristics of fitness. Do these have mental equivalents?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strength: ability to process a large volume of inputs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flexibility: ability to process a wide range of inputs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Endurance: ability to process inputs over periods of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resilience: ability to recover from processing inputs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That all seems right and maybe it can serve as a good foundation, but just as physical fitness has little predictive power in a street fight it seems these markers of mental fitness bare little in common to what we care about when we talk about mental well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/19/Fit-Mind</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/19/Fit-Mind</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Undercharged</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When undercharged for a purchase (cashier mistake for example), what do you do?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many contradictory righteous feelings come flooding in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Surely it is just a make up for the times you were over charged and didn’t notice.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Surely we want to live in a world where honesty and forthrightness prevails.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I win! I win!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Surely the cashier was jeopardizing her employment to make a subtle opening to continue our relationship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, this internal drama a great example of how righteous feelings are not our guide to the moral universe and that often they contain more comedy than wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/18/Undercharged</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/18/Undercharged</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bingeing Podcasts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bingeing podcasts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fan (bordering on obsessed) with podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as is true with most obsessions, terms and conditions for responsible use is generally a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T&amp;amp;C: Binge, extract, and process interesting ideas while on vacation. For god’s sake &lt;strong&gt;do not touch them when in daily life.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Podcasts capture, distract, and twist my mind with exotic thoughts while my values, goals, and objectives get derailed for weeks at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good news however, with this bingeing system I am finding myself coming back from vacations energized, productive, more enthused, and less distractible.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/17/Bingeing-Podcasts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/17/Bingeing-Podcasts</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rule: If it is funny, say it.</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“If it is funny, say it.” R. Gervais&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I imagine one could come up with multitudes of exceptions to this rule. But I posit that many of those exceptions are exactly the situations that humor is most valuable. And if you are afraid of offending or upsetting someone, you are most likely not giving the recipient enough credit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/16/Rule-Funny</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/16/Rule-Funny</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Short v Long</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You can view aspects of life either as a series of many independent games or as one long evolving one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I am inclined towards favoring the long game and I am realizing some of the benefits of doing so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Practice and study don’t make much sense for short independent games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An over-arching sense of calm and it-is-ok-ness is present in the long game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small decisions somehow matter more yet weigh less in longer games because you can imagine them accumulating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/15/Long-Game</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/15/Long-Game</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Practical Sister</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While not learning much of anything mundane or merely practical from my little sister (this is meant to be a veiled compliment), recently I have been writing this blog on the elliptical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The notion that one could maneuver an elliptical, without hands, while thinking, while typing, surely never would have occurred to me without her graceful example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks Jayne. When I win this bet, &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt;, dinner is on me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/14/Practical-Sister</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/14/Practical-Sister</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flyover Message</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, unwillingly engaged in argument with my partner, I was in need of help, cover, air-support, anything to escape the battle with minimal carnage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On cue… Enter flyover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bird dropped two a-bomb sized loads inches from the target.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target was not injured (apart from a little shrapnel lodged in the calf), but the message was received. The battle was over.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/13/Flyover-Message</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/13/Flyover-Message</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Locked Out</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am tired of the split second of panic and dread when I reach down into my pocket and my keys are not there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only to have them be in the other pocket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While eventually mindfulness is the answer to this all to frequent even, in the meantime a more practical measure will be taken: Keys always in the right-hand pocket.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/12/Locked-Out</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//daily/2020/02/12/Locked-Out</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>